<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>news on 대기과학과</title>
    <link>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoskor/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in news on 대기과학과</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 12:49:47 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoskor/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Seminar] Prof. Myung-in Lee</title>
      <link>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoskor/blog/2018/03/18/seminar_leemyungin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 12:49:47 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoskor/blog/2018/03/18/seminar_leemyungin/</guid>
      <description>Korean Heatwaves and Their Association with Large-scale Atmospheric Circulation Patterns 
Prof. Myong-In Lee (Ulsan National Institute of Science and Technology) 2018/3/20 (Tuesday) 16:00 Science Hall #553 
Abstract Heatwave is a natural disaster with prolonged hot weather lasting for a few days or even longer than a few weeks, increasing mortality and heat diseases, as well as many harmful impacts on property loss and daily lives. As the global mean temperature increases especially in recent years, many regions in the globe are suffering from more frequent development of heatwaves and tropical nights with unprecedented intensity during warm season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Seminar] Prof. Michael L. Kaplan</title>
      <link>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoskor/blog/2018/03/17/seminar_kaplan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 18:04:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoskor/blog/2018/03/17/seminar_kaplan/</guid>
      <description>The Unbalanced Dynamics of Deep Jet Streaks Above Developing Surface Inverted Troughs Prof. Michael L. Kaplan (Desert Research Institute) 2018년 3월 21일 (수) 11:00 과학관 553호 Abstract We will employ high resolution observations and numerical simulations to show how the coupling between low-level and mid-tropospheric largely diabatically-forced frontogenesis results in complex upper-tropospheric jet adjustments in two</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>notice format</title>
      <link>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoskor/blog/2015/10/10/notice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2015 13:07:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoskor/blog/2015/10/10/notice/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png  should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png  Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>