<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Faculty on Dep. of Atmos. Sci.</title>
    <link>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoseng/teams/faculty/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Faculty on Dep. of Atmos. Sci.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 13:39:46 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoseng/teams/faculty/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dong-Bin Shin</title>
      <link>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoseng/people/dongbinshin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoseng/people/dongbinshin/</guid>
      <description>Research interests  Satellite Meteorology Atmospheric Remote Sensing Atmospheric Radiation  Education  Ph.D. (1999) Atmospheric Sciences, Texas A&amp;amp;M University, College Station, TX, USA M.S. (1989) Meteorology, Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea B.S. (1987) Astronomy and Meteorology, Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea  Research Experience  2014-present : Professor, Department of Atmospheric Sciences, Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea. 2007-2013 : Associate Professor, Department of Atmospheric Sciences, Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea. 2002-2007 : Research Professor, Center for Earth Observing and Space Research, School of Computational Sciences, George Mason University, Fairfax, VA, USA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hajoon Song</title>
      <link>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoseng/people/hajoonsong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoseng/people/hajoonsong/</guid>
      <description>Research interests  Air-sea interactions Carbon cycle Data assimilation  Education  Ph.D. (2011) Scripps Institution of Oceanography, University of California, San Diego, USA B.S. (2005) Department of Atmospheric Sciences, Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea  Research Experience  MIT, Cambridge, USA (2013-2018) University of California, Santa Cruz, USA (2011-2013) Scripps Institution of Oceanography, La Jolla, USA (2005-2011)  Courses  Air-sea interactions Ocean modeling  Selected Publications  Stukel, M.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hye-Yeong Chun</title>
      <link>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoseng/people/hyeyeongchun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoseng/people/hyeyeongchun/</guid>
      <description>Research interests  Atmospheric Gravity Waves Nonlinear Dynamics of Mesoscale Atmospheric Circulation Cloud Dynamics in Mesoscale Convective System Mountain Waves Atmospheric Solitary Waves Parameterization of Gravity Wave Drag on GCM Middle Atmosphere Dynamics  Education  Ph.D. (1991) in Atmospheric Sciences, North Carolina State University, USA M.Sc (1987) in Meteorology, Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea B.Sc (1985) in Meteorology, Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea  Academic Experience  2003 ~ : Professor, Yonsei University / Editor of KMS 2010 : Visiting Scholar, JPL/NASA/USA 2008 - 2009 : Chair of academic committee, KMS 2004 : Visiting Professor, Kyoto University, Japan 2003 : Visiting Scholar, ATDD/ARL/NOAA/USA 2001 - 2003 : Chairman, Dept.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hyun Mee Kim</title>
      <link>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoseng/people/hyunmeekim/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoseng/people/hyunmeekim/</guid>
      <description>Research interests  Atmospheric Predictability Data Assimilation Adaptive Observation Large and Synoptic Scale Atmospheric Dynamics  Education  Ph.D. (2002) Atmospheric and Oceanic Sciences, University of Wisconsin-Madison, USA M.S. (1992) Atmospheric Sciences, Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea B.S. (1990) Atmospheric Sciences, Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea  Professional Experience  2014-current : Professor, Yonsei University 2009-2014 : Associate professor, Yonsei University 2005-2008 : Assistant professor, Yonsei University 2003-2005 : Research Scientist &amp;amp; Meteorological Administration, Meteorological Research Institute, Korea</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeong Woo Kim</title>
      <link>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoseng/people/jeongwookim/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoseng/people/jeongwookim/</guid>
      <description> Research interests  Atmospheric Dynamics  Education  Ph.D. (1973) Meteorology, University of California, Los Angeles, USA  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jhoon Kim</title>
      <link>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoseng/people/jhoonkim/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoseng/people/jhoonkim/</guid>
      <description>Research interests  Atmospheric Radiation Remote Sensing Ozone layer Aeronomy  Education  Ph.D. (1991) 공과대학 대기. 우주과학, Univ. of Michigan - Ann Arbor, USA M.S. (1987) 공과대학 대기. 우주과학, Univ. of Michigan - Ann Arbor, USA B.S. (1986) Meteorology, Seoul National University, Seoul, Korea  Professional Experience  2003 - current : 연세대학교 대기과학과/지구환경연구소 교수 2014-2015 : 자연과학연구원 부원장, 자연과학융합연구소 소장 2007-2009 : 학과장 1991 - 2003 : 한국항공우주연구원(KARI) 책임연구원, 선임연구원 2009 - 현재 : 환경부 위성사업 연구단장 (P.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jinkyu Hong</title>
      <link>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoseng/people/jinkyuhong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoseng/people/jinkyuhong/</guid>
      <description>Research interests  Carbon and Water Cycles Urban Microclimate Atmospheric Turbulence  Education  Ph.D. (2005) Department of Atmospheric Sciences, Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea M.S. (1999) Department of Atmospheric Sciences, Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea B.S. (1997) Astronomy and Atmospheric Sciences, Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea  Professional Experience  Science Steering Committee Member of AsiaFlux (http://asiaflux.net) (2014-2017) Technical Advisory Committee Member of Korea Institute of Atmospheric Prediction System (http://kiaps.org) (2015-present) Advisory committee member for weather and climate business support center, KMIPA (2015- present) Research proposal investigator in National Research Foundation Organizing committee member of 1st and 2nd Urban and Rural Meteorology Workshop 2012 (http://workshop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ki Ku Cho</title>
      <link>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoseng/people/hikucho/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoseng/people/hikucho/</guid>
      <description> Research interests  Atmospheric Radiation  Education  Ph.D. Meteorology, Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea M.S. Meteorology, Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea B.S. Physics, Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea  Professional Experience  현 연세대학교 명예교수 현 한국기상학회 명예회장 1971 - 1999 연세대학교 대기과학과 교수 1981 - 1982 미국 미시간 대학교 객원교수, 전 한국기상학회장 1958 - 1970 중앙기상대 근무  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sanghun Park</title>
      <link>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoseng/people/sanghunpark/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoseng/people/sanghunpark/</guid>
      <description> Research interests  대기모델링  Education  Ph.D. () Department of Atmospheric Sciences, Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea B.S. () Department of Atmospheric Sciences, Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea  Courses  대기역학  Selected Publications  Publication 1 Publication 2  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seongsoo Yum</title>
      <link>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoseng/people/seongsooyum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoseng/people/seongsooyum/</guid>
      <description>Research interests  Cloud Physics Cloud Observation and numerical modeling Cloud seeding experiment  Education  Ph.D. (1998) Univ. of Nevada, Reno, USA M.Sc. (1986) Dep. of Astronomy &amp;amp; Atmospheric Science, Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea B.Sc. (1984) Dep. of Astronomy &amp;amp; Meteorology, Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea  Work Experience  Yale University in U.S.A (Post Doc. 2001.3-2001.8) Desert Research Institute in U.S.A (Post Doc. 1998.9-2001.3) Metri in KMA, Lab. of App.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seungman Lee</title>
      <link>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoseng/people/seungmanlee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoseng/people/seungmanlee/</guid>
      <description> Research interests Education  Ph.D.  Professional Experience </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Songyou Hong</title>
      <link>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoseng/people/songyouhong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoseng/people/songyouhong/</guid>
      <description> Research interests  Numerical Weather Prediction Regional Climate Parameterization of Atmospheric Physics Seasonal Prediction  Education  Ph.D. (1992) Seoul National University, Seoul, Korea  Professional Experience Selected Publications  Publication 1 Publication 2  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soon-Il An</title>
      <link>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoseng/people/soonilan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoseng/people/soonilan/</guid>
      <description>Research interests  Climate Dynamics Atmosphere Ocean Interaction El Nino, Climate Change Paleoclimate dynamics  Education  Ph.D. (1996) Atmospheric Sciences, Seoul National University, Seoul, Korea M.S. (1991) Atmospheric Sciences, Seoul National University, Seoul, Korea B.S. (1989) Atmospheric Sciences, Seoul National University, Seoul, Korea  Scientific Work Experience  Associate Researcher, International Pacific Research Center, SOEST, University of Hawaii, Honolulu, Hawaii, 2002.10~2005.9 Assistant Researcher, International Pacific Research Center, SOEST, University of Hawaii, Honolulu, Hawaii, 2001.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tae-Young Lee</title>
      <link>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoseng/people/taeyounglee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoseng/people/taeyounglee/</guid>
      <description> Research interests  Mesoscale Meteorology Air Pollution Meteorology Atmospheric Modeling Numerical Weather Prediction  Education  Ph.D. (1984) Oregon State University, Korea  Professional Experience Selected Publications  Publication 1 Publication 2  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yign Noh</title>
      <link>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoseng/people/yignnoh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://web.yonsei.ac.kr/atmoseng/people/yignnoh/</guid>
      <description> Research interests  Geophysical Fluid Dynamics Turbulence Suspension Parallel Computational Fluid Dynamics Physical Oceanography Ocean Mixed Layer OGCM LES  Education  Ph.D. (1987) Department of Earth &amp;amp; Planetary Sciences,The Johns Hopkins University, Baltimore, MD, USA M.Sc. (1982) Department of Physics, Seoul National University, Seoul, Korea. B.Sc. (1980) Department of Oceanography, Seoul National University, Seoul, Korea.  Work Experience Courses  유체역학 전산유체역학 미기상학  Selected Publications  Publication 1 Publication 2  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>